NEEL CHAUDHARI

Brampton, ON L6Y 4R9 | 6479707035 | Neelchaudhari98@gmail.com

Summary

Enthusiastic Computer Technician proudly offering over three years of experience in upgrading systems, installing network components and providing informal software demonstrations. Enthusiastic employee with knowledge in email account setup. Skilled in task prioritization, exemplary customer service and troubleshooting.

Skills

- Troubleshooting
- Active Directory Services
- VPN (Zscaler, Cisco AnyConnect)
- Multifactor Authenticator Tools (Okta, Authenticator)
- Cisco Endpoint Security
- AMP protect
- Microsoft office

- Hard Drive cloning
- Image processing
- Service Now(Helpdesk Software)
- Cisco Network Switches
- Azure AD
- Airwatch Mobility
- Microsoft Intune

Experience

Deskside Support Technician - Contract Acces Employment

01/2022 to 07/2022 Toronto, ON

- Created and updated desktop images for Acces Employment employees.
- Performed re-imaging and diagnostics of desktops and laptops with Microsoft Deployment Toolkit (MDT)
- Install licensed software needed by customer.
- Upgraded, repaired, configured, and installed PCs & Laptops computers Provided user training Coordinated user returns of systems, provided warranty
- Responsible for staging, imaging, testing and deploying new workstations in a zero down time environment.
- Install licensed software needed by employees.
- Configuring DNS issues and wall jack issues while troubleshooting IP addressing problems.

Level 2 Helpdesk Analyst Buchanan Technologies

12/2020 to 01/2022 Charlottetown, PE

- Provide technical assistance and support for incoming queries and issues related to computer systems, software, hardware, Active Directory and VMware
- Provided direction and support to Tier 1 technical support representatives
- Documented thoroughly all incidents in Service Now
- Relate, link and assigned incidents to appropriate teams and escalate when systemic issues were needed
- Maintained call tracking system and KB through the input of resolutions to issues or tracking issues that are escalated to a higher level
- In-depth knowledge of Securing Network, Host, Data and Risk management tool
- Kept user's informed about issue resolution progress and provided updated estimated times of resolution on ongoing basis.
- Reporting on trends and metrics to upper management

Level 1 Helpdesk Analyst Buchanan Technologies

01/2020 to 12/2020 Charlottetown, PE

Troubleshooting and support of software applications, various hardware/software configurations and

- running of appropriate testing and diagnostics
- Presentation of technical knowledge in clear, concise layman terms to non- technologically savvy partners
- Experience Installing and Configuring Operating systems, network and local printers and business applications
- Consulted via telephone to understand user problems, run through testing scripts and ask probing questions to locate root causes.
- Strong experience and good knowledge on the following Microsoft Products (Windows OS, Active Directory, SCCM, MS-Office)
- Experience implementing and supporting Windows and Microsoft Office applications

Field Service Technician

04/2020 to 10/2020 Charlottetown, PE

Bell - Advancetek communication

- Install new products and test them to ensure they are working correctly
- Perform Maintenance and provide customer support
- Diagnose problems and come up with solutions to repair them
- Educating the client on how to use and maintain their device.

Education and Training

Computer Systems Technology

04/2019

George Brown College Toronto, ON

Accomplishments

- Comptia Security +
- HDI Certified